They're heading for a breakdown.
Sacramento is a comedy, drama film directed by Michael Angarano.
When free-spirited Rickey suddenly reappears in father-to-be Glenn’s life, the two
former best friends embark on a spontaneous road trip from LA to Sacramento.
Glenn, played by Michael Cera.
Rickey, played by Michael Angarano.
Tallie, played by Maya Erskine.
Rosie, played by Kristen Stewart.
Arielle, played by April Jeanette Mendez.
Jess, played by Iman Karam.
Sacramento is a 2024 American road comedy film directed by Michael
Angarano, who wrote the screenplay with Chris Smith.
It stars Michael Cera, Angarano, Maya Erskine and Kristen Stewart.
The film explores themes of road trip, los angeles, california,
former best friend, buddy comedy, independent film.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.